universalcycles.com 2006-11-23

# Universal Cycles - Our Privacy Policy

* * *

* * *

**Shop By Company:**  
  
**Full Company List**

* * *

| 

Our Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy Statement**

Here at Universal Cycles, we're proud of the relationships we've made with our customers. Part of that relationship is our commitment to respect your privacy. We promise to always be truthful in our mailing practices in order to continue that strong relationship. We always use industry-standard encryption technology when transferring and receiving consumer data. We also have rigorous security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we receive from our customers.

If you have any questions regarding this policy, please don't hesitate to contact us at:

5929 N.E. 80th St Portland, OR 97218 or 800 936 5156  fax 503 296 2473 or Email us at Sales@universalcycles.com

Frequently Asked Questions:

What information do you collect?  
We collect the e-mail addresses of those visitors who volunteer information about themselves through programs such as survey information, site registrations, and newsletter subscribers. Our Web server DOES NOT automatically recognize information regarding the domain or e-mail address of visitors. Universal Cycles e-mail newsletters and promotions are strictly opt-in and require a log-in and password. If you signed up, but now wish to be removed, please contact us.  
  
Do you share this information with other companies?  
The personal information is not shared with any third parties

Will I be contacted if I give you my phone number?  
Customers that offer their phone numbers online will only receive phone calls from us with information regarding orders they've placed online. If you do not want to receive such phone calls please contact us.

What about my postal address?  
If you supply us with your postal address online, you may receive periodic mailings and catalogs from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not want to receive these mailings, please contact us and asked to be removed.

Please provide us with your exact name and address as it appears on the mailing label. We will be sure to remove your name from the list we share with other organizations as well.

Are My orders secure?  
Yes, All orders are processed using SSL secure socket layer technology.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, please contact us at the above addresses and phone numbers

Acceptance of Privacy Policy Terms and Conditions

By using this site, you agree to the terms and conditions of the above privacy policy. If you do not agree with this policy, please do not use this site. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes on our Website. Customers will always have the opportunity to opt-out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, please check back with our Website periodically
